

VIRANDA SOONTHORNPAKDEE

PROJECT MANAGER | UX/UI DESIGNER

CONTACT

Bangkok, Thailand 064-451-9941 viranda.soonthornpakdee@gmail.com www.viranda.me

MY PROFILE

My name is Viranda and you can call me Dao, 27 years old. Over 5 years of experience in the Digital Industry. I've been doing many roles starting from UX/UI Designer and got promote tp Project Manager/Product Owner. I able to effectively coordinate tasks to accomplish projects with timeliness and creativity. My greatest strength is solid organisational skills including attention to detail and multi-tasking skills, Strong aptitude and desire to learn new technologies and tools.



SKILLS

- Software Project Management
- User Interface Design
- User Experience (UX)
- Web Design
- Software Design
- CSS

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Sketch
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustration
- Adobe After Effect

INTERESTS

- Design Trends
- HTML/CSS
- New Technologies Tools
- English Practice

CERTIFICATES

Design Thinking

Thammasart University

• Foundation of User Experience Design

Coursera By Google

EXPERIENCES

Feb 2020-Now

SENIOR UX/UI DESIGNER (BUZZEBEES CO.,LTD.)

Ability in Design Thinking methodology full loop (User Research, Define a problem, Ideation, Wireframe, Prototype, and Testing) And collaborator with vendors to control performance and usability in the UI UX part. Design on web base in LINE Platform

June 2018 - Jan 2020

PROJECT MANAGER / PRODUCT OWNER (BANGKOKSOLUTIONS CO.,LTD.)

As a project Manager with designing background. I used to handle many types of tasks such as web design, application design and software design & development. I able to effectively coordinate tasks to accomplish projects with timeliness and creativity. My greatest strength is solid organisational skills including attention to detail and multi-tasking skills.

June 2016 - Jan 2020

SENIOR UX/UI DESIGNER (BANGKOKSOLUTIONS CO.,LTD.)

As an UX/UI Designer with an eye for great user interface design and have a passion for pixel-perfect precision. I'm dedicated to provide the best solution with great user experience. I'm working closely to developer to understand the depth of business and to make sure the scope and the direction of the product is aligned and within schedule. I have a little knowledge of HTML and CSS. so I can help reduce the developer's work and I can understand the database tables meanings and relationships.

EDUCATIONS

2021 - 2015

BACHELOR DEGREE OF FINE AND APPLIED ART

Burapha University

2009 - 2012

ENGLISH - JAPANESE LANGUAGE AND LITERATURE

Satrinonthaburi School